

Mohammad Rizal Ardiansyah

August 21, 2000 (+62) 83847544225 linkedin/in/mohammadrizala mohammadrizala@gmail.com Jl. Kol. Hadijanto No. 117 Banaran Sekaran, Gunungpati, Kota Semarang. 50229

Profile

Final-year Geography Student with an interest in research, writing, surveying, and mapping. I have participated in several internships and worked in terms of spatial data processing, data collection, website management, media management, and content writing. Likes to learn new things, think critically, and be proficient in problem solving.

Educational Background

Universitas Negeri Semarang

Major in Geography 2019 - Now GPA 3.63/4.00

SMA Negeri 1 Genteng

Major in Social Science 2016 - 2019

Skills & Ability

- GIS Software (ArcGIS, QGIS, and Google Earth Engine)
- WeGIS Development (Leaflet, and Open Layers)
- Web Development (Html, CSS, and JavaScript)
- Database (Geoserver and PostgeSQL/PostGIS)
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, and PowerPoint)

Certification

Drone Pilot Certification 2023

Drone Edutech

Portfolio

My Portfolio

Work Experience

Kabarbuana.com

Editorial Secretary and Content Writer December 2022 - September 2023

- Write Articles
- Research keyword for daily content
- Create content writer productivity reports
- Managing advertising and social media

Badan Pusat Statistik (BPS)

Field Data Officer on Social and Economic Registration October 2022 - November 2022

- Collect population data in the census area
- Geotagging every resident's house
- Recapitulate the results of field data collection

CV Citarasa Rempah Indonesia (REINA)

Internship as Admin And Web Optimize *July 2022 - October 2022*

- Manage and maintain the company website
- Optimizing the appearance and performance of the company website
- Optimizing SEO on the company website

Direktorat Jenderal Tata Ruang, Kementerian ATR/BPN

Internship In Spatial Planning for Regional and National Growth (INSPIRING)

February 2022 - July 2022

- Manage the spatial database of Spatial Planning And Regional Planning maps
- Adjusting the plan book and analysis fact book with the new rules
- Collecting supporting data in the preparation of Spatial Planning And Regional Planning